# Laura Zodrow

## UI/UX Designer and Front-End Developer

Denver, CO

http://laurazodrow.com

laura.zodrow@gmail.com

832.922.2053

#### **ABOUT**

I have over four years of experience designing websites and developing products. I am looking for a position that allows me to design using my UI/UX skills and implement my designs using cutting-edge tools that are developing in the Javascript ecosystem.

#### **SKILLS**

## Designer

User Research Information Architecture Wireframe Production Web Design Prototyping

Interaction Design Usability Testing Adobe Photoshop Sketch InVision

## Developer

JavaScript HTML CSS React.js Redux

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# Software Engineer

Aetna - Denver, CO

June 2017 - Current

Currently collaborating with design and product to create features for Aetna's new medical application. The application uses React, Redux, Webpack and makes API calls to Aetna's back-end services.

## Software Engineer

ReadyTalk - Denver, CO

December 2015 - May 2017

Designed and implemented a checkout portal for our newest product FoxDen. Using React, Node, Express, and making third party calls to Recurly's api. Created the FoxDen website using Phenomic, a modern website generator based on the React and Webpack ecosystem. Also, worked with our back-end engineers to set up the deploy- ment pipeline (using Jenkins, Docker, and AWS).

# Web Developer

Black Dog Digital - Denver, CO

February 2015 - December 2015

Develop Wordpress websites, including a project using component based techniques. Create custom Word- press themes, using HTML5 and CSS3 to implement design specs. Use jQuery to do DOM manipulation and attach event handlers. Write client side PHP scripts making database calls and doing data manipulation. Lead Developer on

http://www.spindenver.com

#### Web Developer

Roots Elementary - Denver, CO

Desiged and collaborated to create scheduling and student monitoring application for Roots Elementary, Charter School in Denver, CO. Implemented client side Google OAuth and integrated with Google calendar API. Also, integrated with third party scanning software. Application uses jQuery, Node.js, Express, MongoDB, and Web Sockets.

# Assistant Product Manager

AA Concepts - Houston, TX

September 2012 - December 2013

Created the graphics for the Langford Market website, developing my interest in web design and development. Also booked, directed, and styled Langford Market photo shoots, and assisted the Brand Manager in planning and executing all marketing and promotional events.

## Gallery Assistant

michelle y williams - Houston, TX

September 2011 - December 2012

Designed ads and artwork promotional slips for opening events. Built client relationships for current and future art sales. Also, represented the company at art fairs, both domestically and internationally.

#### **EDUCATION**

DesignLab: UX Research & Strategy DesignLab: UX: Interaction Design

RefactorU: 10-week Full-Stack JavaScript Development course

Bachelor of Arts: Austin College, Sherman, TX (Graduated May 2011)

- Major in Political Science; Minor in Italian Studies
- International Educational Studies, Rome, Italy (2009–2010)